http://www.loverboysusa.com/privacy.html

LoverboysUSA.com Privacy Policy
Last updated: 1st September 2013
Privacy policy statement for casual visitors to our website, we do not collect any information regarding domains, email addresses, or any other personal details.
The information that we collect from our customers is not shared with other organisations for commercial purposes. If you do not want to receive e-mail, mailings, or telephone calls - if you supplied us with those details - from us in the future, please contact us and we will remove you from any mailing lists.
LoverboysUSA.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our customers. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our websites.
Automatically collected information
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and keep track of how many visitors our websites have had, what country they have come from and what browser version they use. At no time is your IP address used to help identify you.
IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.
Cookies
We use cookies to help maintain a consistent experience for our customers. Cookies are used throughout our site to enable us to keep track of options selected by you. At no time is any personal information stored within a cookie. Visitors to our site can refuse cookies by turning them off in their browser, please note this will result in various aspects or our site becoming inaccessible due to relying on cookies for functionality.
Cookies are small text files stored on your computer by your web browser software.
Personal information
Our website uses a basic contact form for customers to request information about our products and services and also to request general information. We do not collect and store visitors' personal contact information.
Registered users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. The information that you provide to us will not be shared or sold to any other company or individuals at any time.
Security
All Payments from this site are made via CCBill, or NetBilling. When you make a purchase you will be taken to a secure server. Depending on your web browser you will see a small padlock that informs you that your information is encrypted and you are on a secure server (SSL). Also, in the address bar the URL should start with "https://". VXSBill and CCBill only use the highest level of Internet security. At no time will your information be in any danger of theft.
Public forums
We do not have any forums, guest books or message boards on this site. Under no circumstances will information passed to LoverboysUSA.com from online forms, postal order forms or from any other source be made public.
Advertisers
This site does not use third party ad companies to display advertisements on our site. However we do have outside companies advertising in our resources section (link exchange pages) these companies may use cookies and other information gathering methods to target ads to visitors.
External Links
LoverboysUSA.com's site contains links to other sites. LoverboysUSA.com is not responsible for the privacy policies, privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you do not wish to be placed on our mailing list please make sure you have opted by contacting us.
Contacting the website
If at any time you wish to contact us with a membership issue, please login to the members area and send us a message from the contact form provided. If you are having issues gaining access then please direct all queries to the billing support pages.
Billing Support
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
18 U.S.C. Section 2257
Our Friends
Link Exchange
Copyright © 2012 LoverboysUSA.com. All Rights Reserved.
All graphics, layouts, and advertising text on this site are copyrighted. All violators
are subject to legal penalties for copyright violations, and will be prosecuted to the
fullest extent of the law.
Sitemaps:
